<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Snap It</string>
    <string name="Api_key">CgB6e3x9a4NNICDnGnFCV8+aBktmeoZWbiCIcGNQgzzmkzM2oPozCF5/YlX0DsOMAdd+6rsKevlDLTYy5ROFchTz</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="ad_id_native">testy63txaom86</string>
    <string name="ad_id_native_small">testb65czjivt9</string>
    <string name="ad_id_native_video">testy63txaom86</string>
    <string name="ad_flag">Ad</string>

    <string-array name="setting_array">
        <item>Privacy Policy</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="icon">
        <item>Restaurant</item>
        <item>Petrol Station</item>
        <item>Shop</item>
        <item>Museum</item>
        <item>Hotel</item>
        <item>Hospital</item>
        <item>Cinema</item>
        <item>Bank</item>
        <item>Amusement Park</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="articelTitle">
        <item>My 50 Best Travel Tips After 10 Years Traveling The World</item>
        <item>Everything you should and shouldn’t do to stay healthy on a plane</item>
        <item>7 essential travel safety tips</item>
        <item>5 Ways to Save and Spend Wisely When Traveling</item>
        <item>Planes, Trains and Automobiles: Which Mode of Transport is Best for Your Travel Plans?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="articelContain">
        <item>
            TRAVEL TIPS GUIDE\n
            It’s now been 10 years since I sold everything and left the United States to travel the world. These are the best travel tips to help you save money and have a great trip.\n\n
            Curious about how to travel the world? I’ve been traveling around the world for many years as a digital nomad.\n\n
            <b>And I have tons of useful travel tips to share from my journey.</b>\n\n
            My traveling started when I quit my job and took a one-way flight from Miami to Guatemala, leaping nervously into the unknown and leaving much of my old life behind while embarking on an epic adventure around the world.\n\n
           <b>The experience has been a wild ride — traveling to over 50 countries, meeting countless people, and I’ve learned a ton since I first left!</b>\n\n
            Having adventures like hitchhiking across America, camping alone in Greenland, trekking through Afghanistan and much more — the world has been an amazing teacher.\n\n
            I eventually turned writing about my journey into a successful travel blog, and continue to travel on a regular basis as part of my dream job.\n\n
            But to celebrate my travelversary (travel anniversary) each year, I update this guide with a collection of my best travel tips to help you save money, stay safe, and inspire others to get out there and explore our world.\n\n
            And feel free to share your own favorite travel tips in the comments at the end!\n\n
            <big><b>TIPS FOR MAKING TRAVEL EASY AND FUN\n\n</b></big>
            1: Patience Is Important\n2: Wake Up Early To Avoid Crowds\n3: Observe Daily Life Around You\n
            4: Laugh At Yourself Sometimes\n5: Slow Down To Enjoy Your Trip\n6: Volunteer Occasionally\n
            7: Take Lots Of Epic Travel Photos\n8: Don’t Get Discouraged\n9: Break Out Of Your Comfort Zone\n
            10: Keep An Open Mind\n11: Get Lost On Purpose\n12: Be Flexible and Don’t Over Plan\n
            13: Learn A Few Foreign Words\n14: Take An Extra Credit and ATM Card\n15: Write Down The Address Of Your Hotel\n
            16: Read A Book About The Country\n17: Splurge A Bit While Traveling\n18: Pack Ear Plugs and  An Eye Mask\n
            19: Take A Scarf Or Sarong With You\n20: Bring Your Own Water Bottle\n21: Pack Less Stuff In Your Backpack\n
            22: Carry Spare Passport Photos\n23: Bring An Extra Camera Battery\n24: Always Pack A Lock\n
            25: Bring Good Travel Shoes\n26: Packing Cubes For The Win!\n27: Book The Cheapest Flights\n
            28: Go On Free Walking Tours\n29: Eat Local Food Frequently\n30: Avoid Expensive Hotels and Resorts\n
            31: Cook Your Own Meals\n32: Use Travel Credit Cards For Rewards\n33: Eat Away From Tourist Attractions\n
            34: Don’t Be Afraid Of Other Countries\n35: Always Get Travel Insurance\n36: Wear That Sunscreen!\n
            37: Stash Extra Cash For Emergencies\n38: Back Up Your Files and Photos!\n39: Treat Your Body Well\n
            40: Get Your Vaccinations\n41: Travel By Yourself Occasionally\n42: Get Off The Beaten Path\n
            43: Stay In Touch With Loved Ones\n44: Make Friends With Locals\n45: Listen To Podcasts For Long Trips\n
            46: Say Yes More Often\n47: Visit The Local Tourism Office\n48: Get A Comfortable Travel Pillow\n
            49: Follow The Business Travelers\n50: Stay Hydrated.\n

        </item>
        <item>
            After the historic drop in air travel this spring, Americans are steadily flying again — some with mixed reviews.\n\n
            After flying for work a few times and once to see family in California, Kyle Potter, editor of the Thrifty Traveler, says he’s not eager to get back on a plane anytime soon. With every airline carrying out coronavirus precautions differently, “you just don’t know what you’re going to find,” Potter says.\n\n
            Potter’s main takeaway from his recent flying experience has been for travelers to do their homework ahead of a flight, checking to see what rules an airline has in place for blocking middle seats and mask enforcement. Additionally, Potter says that “people should listen to public health experts.”\n\n
            Before booking your flight, know that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention still says travel increases your chance of getting and spreading covid-19, and that nearly 11,000 people have been exposed to the coronavirus on flights. But according to an October 1 article in JAMA, “the risk of contracting coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) during air travel is lower than from an office building, classroom, supermarket, or commuter train.”\n\n
            ″We want to make sure people understand that the risk [of catching coronavirus while traveling] will never be zero,” says Syra Madad, who was recently featured in Netflix docuseries “Pandemic: How to Prevent an Outbreak.” “But there’s ways that you can help reduce or mitigate some of that risk by layering on different types of basic approaches.”\n\n
            Here are some of those approaches you need to know about staying healthy on a plane.\n\n
            <big><b>WEAR THE REQUIRED PPE\n\n</b></big>
            At this time, most airlines are requiring passengers wear masks to fly, a move that health experts applaud.\n\n
            “Always wear a mask, not just on the plane, but off the plane in the airport, waiting in the lobby areas as well,” says Alvin Tran, an assistant professor of public health at the University of New Haven School of Health Sciences in Connecticut.\n\n
            Travelers can also wear additional personal protective equipment, such as face shields, for extra protection on board.\n\n
            “We know that covid-19 spreads by touching your mucous membranes, and your eyes are obviously one part of your mucous membranes,” says Madad, noting she doesn’t discourage the use of a face shield onboard planes. “It’s better to be overprotected than underprotected, especially if you’re traveling to an area with high community transmission.”\n\n
            Tran agrees. “If you are comfortable wearing a face shield and you don’t think it’s going to bother you, then I don’t see a reason why you wouldn’t want to wear that,” he says.\n\n
            But experts do recommend against travelers wearing hazmat suits during flights.\n\n
            <big><b>MAINTAIN GOOD HAND HYGIENE\n\n</b></big>
            Washing your hands properly is one of the best ways to protect yourself from spreading diseases. The CDC recommends washing your hands “often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds, especially after going to the bathroom; before eating; and after blowing your nose, coughing or sneezing.”\n\n
            “If I were to travel, I would make sure that I am washing my hands very frequently,” Tran says. If you don’t have access to soap and water, opt for an alcohol-based hand sanitizer with at least 60 percent alcohol.\n\n
            <big><b>WIPE DOWN COMMUNAL SURFACES\n\n</b></big>
            Once upon a time, it seemed excessive to wipe down your personal space on an airplane. In the wake of the coronavirus, the practice is now being recommended by health professionals.\n\n
            Robert Quigley, regional medical director for travel risk mitigation company International SOS, told The Post that “thoroughly wiping down surfaces while traveling is ‘always in order,’ because many viruses and bacteria can survive on objects.”\n\n
            The CDC is urging people to clean and disinfect frequently used objects and surfaces that you touch with your hands, so bring disinfectant wipes on board if you’ll be using an in-flight entertainment system or tray table.\n\n
            <big><b>CHOOSE A WINDOW SEAT\n\n</b></big>
            Health experts say that the riskiest parts of traveling by plane take place before and after a flight due to crowding. Do your best to maintain social distance from other travelers as you go through airport security, check bags, board the plane, collect your bag at the luggage carousel and leave the airport.\n\n
            Some medical professionals recommend reserving a window seat on a plane to avoid catching an illness in-flight, noting that aisle seats have more access to potentially-sick passengers.\n\n
            Vicki Hertzberg, a professor in Emory University’s School of Nursing, and the first author on a Boeing-funded study on transmission of respiratory diseases on planes published two years ago, told The Post: “The strategy I take now for flying is: I take a window seat, and I don’t get up.”\n\n
            But the World Health Organization has said “research has shown that there is very little risk of any communicable disease being transmitted on board an aircraft,” thanks to planes’ high-efficiency particulate air filters.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Travel can be an exciting, eye-opening experience. It is easy to get caught up in the thrill of adventure. But don not forget about travel security and safety considerations while you are abroad.\n\n
            Follow these 7 travel safety tips to help you take a trip that is memorable for all the right reasons.\n\n
            <big><b>1. DO YOUR RESEARCH\n\n</b></big>
            Get to know your destination in depth before you arrive. Read traveler reviews and consult with locals for information about the safest neighborhoods, places to stay and incidences of crime. Check the State Department\'s website for country updates and enroll in the Smart Traveler Enrollment Program (STEP).\n\n
            Another important travel security precaution is to know whom to call in an emergency. Get the contact information for the nearest embassy or consulate, police station, and other local emergency departments.\n\n
            <big><b>2. DON NOT DRAW ATTENTION\n\n</b></big>
            People who look like they are from out of town are especially vulnerable to crime, so try to blend in as much as you can. Choose inconspicuous clothing that would not attract attention. Be discreet when looking at maps and approach people carefully if you need to ask for directions.\n\n
            Also consider investing in protective clothing and gear that will make it more difficult for pickpockets to steal money and other personal items.\n\n
            <big><b>3. MAKE COPIES OF IMPORTANT DOCUMENTS\n\n</b></big>
            You never know when you might need a copy of your passport, driver\’s license or another form of identification. Scan these documents to save online and print out several hard copies. That way, you won\’t be scrambling to find proper documentation if you need to get home.\n\n
            <big><b>4. KEEP YOUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY UPDATED\n\n</b></big>
            No matter whether you are going, on an overnight jaunt or a month-long international journey, it is always a good idea to let friends or family back home know. Before you leave, send a copy of your itinerary to a few trusted people who can keep tabs on your whereabouts. Check in regularly with your contacts so they know you are where you are supposed to be.\n\n
            <big><b>5. BE WARY OF PUBLIC WI-FI\n\n</b></big>
            Don not let the convenience of Internet access cloud your judgment. When you use public Wi-Fi, hackers looking to steal valuable information can access your data including credit card or Social Security numbers. If you do need wireless Internet service, set up a virtual private network (VPN) that will allow you to access the Internet securely while traveling.\n\n
            <big><b>6. SAFEGUARD YOUR HOTEL ROOM\n\n</b></big>
            Even if your hotel has strong security measures in place, there are steps you can take to make your room safer. Lock and dead-bolt the door and keep your windows shut. You can buy a jammer, which is a portable device that slips under the door for another layer of protection.\n\n
            Try to give the impression that you are in your room even when you’re away, such as placing the Do Not Disturb sign on the outside of your door and keeping the blinds or windows closed.\n\n
            Don not let any strangers into your room, even if they say they work for the hotel. You can always call the front desk to check whether someone was ordered by hotel staff to come to your room.\n\n
            <big><b>7. BE AWARE OF YOUR SURROUNDINGS\n\n</b></big>
            Don not let your guard down to snap the perfect picture for your social media platforms. Keep an eye on your personal belongings at all times and use good judgment when talking to strangers. A big part of the joy of traveling is the opportunities it affords to meet new people and learn about their cultures. But if someone near you is acting suspiciously, or if you feel uncomfortable, leave the area immediately.\n\n
            Following these tips can help you travel safely, but no matter how many precautions you take the unexpected can always happen. Stay protected with travel insurance from Nationwide, and get peace of mind no matter where you go.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Travel is one of the most amazing gifts you can give yourself. There is just something so exciting about booking a ticket and planning a vacation to some exotic faraway location. But before you buy that dream trip, it is important to do some financial pre-planning so you don\’t end up regretting your holiday when you get home to the credit card bills. As such, we\’ve sat down with Elisabeth Dawson, the founder of COPIA Wealth Management and Insurance Services and the author of the new book Wealth By Design, to get the scoop on saving before and then spending wisely while traveling. Dawson\’s company provides financial and insurance advising with education to help her clients achieve their desired wealth goals using a macroeconomic approach that starts with a \“Wish List.\” Here are her five top tips.\n\n
            <big><b>TIP #1: BUDGET IN ADVANCE\n\n</b></big>
            Start by budgeting to save monthly so that you are not using credit to pay for your \“Great Experience.\”\n\n
            \“Be mindful of exactly what you are going to give yourself as a budget to spend on your trip prior to going so that you do not regress to using credit cards,\” Dawson says.\n\n
            <big><b>TIP #2: CHANGE CURRENCY BEFORE DEPARTING\n\n</b></big>
            Always call your bank prior to traveling outside the country to make an appointment to exchange your money into the currency that you will use in that country.\n\n
            \“It is better to do this in advance so that you save money on bank ATM international transaction fees, airport currency exchanges that charge you a fee on your exchange (you lose money), or not being able to find a bank that will exchange currency for you.  Be prepared and work with all of your money not just a portion of it,\” say says.\n\n
            <big><b>TIP #3: DON\'T OVERSPEND\n\n</b></big>
            Here Dawson says it is important to create a daily budget and stick to it:\n\n
            \“Give yourself a daily budget that you are allowing yourself to spend each day.  Again, save for that freedom while you are on the road.  Breakfast, lunch, and dinner, plus activities and shopping that you want to do should all be allocated. I have a cousin, who when she travels with her husband, creates a budget that she allows them to spend per day for the entire trip. They never go over budget when they travel and allow themselves to splurge at the end from not overspending on the days that they didn\’t spend as much as they budgeted.  This makes sense for everyone.  Having cash along the way or a specific account that allows you the freedom to only spend what you have set aside for your vacation experience is critical.  Know your limitations.\”\n\n
            <big><b>TIP #4: KNOW YOUR BANK\n\n</b></big>
            If you need to change money on the road you can save on fees by using banks with reciprocal agreements to yours at home while traveling.\n\n
            \“If you bank with sister banks while traveling you are not going to be charged fees and or even international exchange rate fees, which can add up quickly,\” Dawson says.\n\n
            <big><b>TIP #5: HAVE FUND!\n\n</b></big>
            And finally, Dawson suggests to not forget to enjoy yourself.\n\n
            \“There are so many free things in every city that you go to any country you visit.  Remember traveling is all about the experience.  Check out the area prior to going and see what you can get to do on a discount or for free.  You will be surprised.\”\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            When embarking on an international trip, you can easily get inundated with big decisions.\n\n
            - Should I spend for a five-star hotel?\n
            - Should I cut out this activity in favor of another?\n
            - How much time can I take off work?\n\n
            But despite all of these decisions, the end-all always circles back to money, and when you\’re spending a lot on a trip, it\’s important to make budget cuts wherever you can. Enter transportation: the single biggest budget-buster on any trip. Regardless of if you stay in a fancy resort or an Airbnb, your flight will likely be your biggest travel expense. What then happens when you need to get around the country? Surely, additional travel will drive you bankrupt? Not exactly.\n\n
            With so many different modes of transport available to get around a country — some pricey and quick, others cheap and long-haul — it\’s hard to decide which is best for you. However, there are distinct and important pros and cons to each that can help you decide when is the time to splurge, and when is the time to hold your wallet a little bit closer.\n\n
            <big><b>PLANES\n\n</b></big>
            Easily the quickest and most effective, planes are the obvious go-to when it comes to travel. Our minds are programmed to associate airline tickets with travel, mostly because we usually need a plane to get to our destinations. When we travel to and from a country, it\’s almost inevitable that we\’ll need to book a flight, but travel within the country can be a bit more variable. Some countries offer domestic flights as cheap as $20 (depending on where you are), while others can cost you up to $400. Opting for buses and trains over planes for domestic travel will minimize transport costs as much as possible, but it always comes at the expense of time and comfort.\n\n
            <b>Plane Pros\n</b>
            Travel by plane is the quickest and most comfortable way to get across a country, often turning a 12+ hour bus ride into a 1-hour trip. They\’re all set for you, have easily trackable and distinct schedules, and are generally very reliable. They’re the no-fuss choice for a busy backpacker who doesn\’t have time to muck about with long highway trips.\n\n
            <b>Plane Cons\n</b>
            Because it\’s the fastest and most comfortable option, air travel will almost always be the most expensive option available to you. In places like the US or Canada, a one-way trip can get as expensive as $400, so it won’t be the most budget-friendly choice.\n\n
            <b><i>When to Opt for a Plane\n</i></b>
            We recommend that you use a plane for domestic travel when you have a very short vacation period and need to get somewhere quick. When you have the luxury of a long vacation, time is a less valuable resource because you simply have more of it, but short trips make your time the most valuable resource you have. If you\’re going somewhere for a week or less, splurge and just get to where you need to go.\n\n
            <big><b>TRAIN\n\n</b></big>
            Trains come in all different shapes and sizes, and that’s even more prominent when you\’re abroad. A train ride in Sweden, for example, will be very, very different from a train ride in India. Nevertheless, trains are always a reliable means of transport when you\’re looking to get somewhere in a moderate amount of time with a moderate amount of comfort. Because they run on their own tracks, they bypass traffic and are therefore probably the fastest method of ground transport that you can find.\n\n
            <b>Train Pros\n</b>
            Probably the second-fastest mode of transport other than a plane, trains will get you where you need to go as quickly as possible on land. There’s no traffic, they\’re generally running on a timely schedule with minimum stops along the way. You know exactly where you\’re getting on and exactly where you\’ll be getting off. Also, they usually have bathrooms included, which can be a huge plus on a long-haul ride (see Buses below).\n\n
            <b>Train Cons\n</b>
            Because trains are usually the fastest mode of land travel, they\’re also usually the most expensive. There are obviously all types of price options depending on your expected level of comfort and seat selection, but they generally are more expensive than buses. Also, because they don’t stop in many places, when you get on a train you’re on it for the long haul. You best make sure that your destination is a stop on the train route, or you can go right past it and have to backtrack. In addition, trains are large and therefore have a lot of people on them. You can have more of a chance of being pickpocketed with so many people around you. We recommend having your most precious belongings (passport, phone, wallet) on your person at all times to avoid this.\n\n
            <b><i>When to Opt for a Train\n</i></b>
            Trains are a lovely middle ground between booking a pricey flight and riding a cheap bus. They\’re a somewhat conservative budgetary option that doesn\’t have to compromise comfort and speed for the money. If you have a week or two on your trip and a moderate budget, We\’d suggest picking a train and saving a bit of time.\n\n
            <big><b>BUSES\n\n</b></big>
            Ahh, buses… cheap, fun and brimming with people. Buses and night buses are easily the most thrifty option for the frugal traveler who wants to save precious pennies that could otherwise be spent on food or sightseeing. But, depending on what you book, buses can be pretty grim. If you\’re not used to long, bumpy bus rides (we\’re talking 12+ hours) avoid sleeper buses and try and find tourist buses that may be slightly more expensive, but would come with amenities such as air conditioning and reclinable seats. All in all, when it comes to bus travel, there\’s a wide range of options; they\’re also a bit of a gamble but definitely a solid choice for anyone who has a bit more time and a bit less money.\n\n
            <b>Plane Pros\n</b>
            Buses are easily the cheapest option for travel that you’ll find in any country. Whether you splurge on a $30 tourist bus or a $3 local bus, there’s no denying that this mode of transport will save you the most money. Some are air-conditioned and have a bathroom; some are sleeper buses that have reclining seats and allow you to sleep (which can save you a night\’s worth of hotel/hostel money), and some have free WiFi. Be sure to check the bus company\’s online reviews to know what amenities will be available to you.\n\n
            <b>Plane Cons\n</b>
            As with any other budget-conscious option, buses come with a laundry list of downsides. They usually are the longest and most tedious transport option, often stopping to pick up locals along the way. They can be wildly uncomfortable (i.e. local night bus, crammed with a stranger for 12 hours), and they can sometimes be jam-packed with people, leaving you susceptible to pickpockets. Keep in mind that even long-haul bus rides may not have bathrooms and will only make occasional stops for them and that booking VIP Buses often don\’t mean anything extravagant or luxurious.\n\n
            <b><i>When to Opt for a Plane\n</i></b>
            Although they come with a lot of risks, buses are definitely the most cost-effective way to travel for the gap-year backpacker who doesn\’t have a lot of money to spend. If you find yourself with two weeks or more and need to count your change, bite the bullet and take the bus; ultimately it will be worth it. Please keep in mind that it\’s always useful to check company reviews online to see what you\’re getting into, and that doesn\’t mean going to the bus company’s self-promoted website. Do your research and go in with few expectations.\n\n
            <big><b>BOATS\n\n</b></big>
            Along the same line as buses, boats can vary in size and experience. We can mention both horror stories of ferry rides that were overpopulated and dirty, and amazing experiences abroad fancy and comfortable luxury boats. Boats are limited in scope, as they can really only take you across the water, but they can also be invaluable assets for cheap travel when your destination is an ocean, lake or river away.\n\n
            <b>Boat Pros\n</b>
            Boat prices can vary depending on how luxurious you’d like your journey to be, but there are many options that can be even cheaper than a bus ride. They can take you clear across rivers and bodies of water way faster than a bus can get around them, and they can even save you accommodation money if you opt for overnight ferry rides.\n\n
            <b>Boat Cons\n</b>
            There\’s no way around it: seasickness is a real factor here. They can also be very overcrowded and occasionally sub-par on the cleanliness front. Overall, with ferries, you get what you pay for. If you pay for a budget ferry, don\’t expect any fancy accommodations. There are even ferries that only have hammocks as beds.\n\n
            <b><i>When to Opt for a Boat\n</i></b>
            For starters, if you\’re prone to getting seasick, boats are never a good option. But, if you can manage it, bite the bullet and choose to sail one when the water option is faster than the land one. Also, there may be some destinations that can only be reached by boat (some islands off the coasts of Colombia or Thailand, for example), so it\’s worth the perceived discomfort if it gets you where you want to go.\n\n
            <big><b>CAR SERVICES\n\n</b></big>
            Car hires, which mean anything from a taxi cab to an Uber or a tuk-tuk, are excellent and cheap ways to get around town for a day trip. While less of an option for a city-to-city trip, hiring a car is a cheap, fast and comfortable option. However, usually you\’ll find yourself hiring a car or cab to get you from your hotel to an attraction and back again, and there are tremendous amounts of difference in price points depending on which you go with.\n\n
            <b>Car Hire Pros\n</b>
            Car hires are perfect when you want to go at your own pace, as you\’re not really abiding by any hurried schedule. You also have more comfort and much less squeezing in with strangers. Ubers, tuk-tuks and other rideshare apps are your best bet for a cheap ride, as they\’re generally cheaper than taxi cabs, especially at airports. Also, depending on which type you use (specifically tuk-tuks), you can often haggle with the driver to bring down the price of your ride.\n\n
            Also, if you have plans to explore an attraction during the day and want the convenience of knowing how to get back, you can hire a driver to take you there, wait for you, and take you back, totally eliminating the guesswork involved in getting a return ride.\n\n
            <b>Car Hire Cons\n</b>
            Unfortunately, because most car hires work their own schedules, most won\’t want to drive hours away to another city, so they usually limit you to the confines of the city you\’re in. They can also be pricey depending on how far you\’re going and which type of car hire you go for (as mentioned before, taxi cabs are generally pretty expensive). Also, if you do hire a driver for the day, you\’ll be paying more, as you\’re paying for the driver\’s waiting time for you in addition to the rides there and back, so it may wind up not being the most frugal option.\n\n
            <b><i>When to Opt for a Car Service\n</i></b>
            Car hires are an excellent resource for when you want to do a quick day trip and avoid inflated tour bus prices. You\’ll get where you\’re going quick and usually have no issue getting back afterward as well, all from the comfort of a private cab.\n\n
            Whether you wind up using car hires, buses, trains or planes–transportation can be a big budgetary issue on your mind. Although, you can potentially save literally hundreds if not thousands of dollars by taking budget-friendly buses or trains but you run the risk of losing valuable time on trips by doing so. At the end of the day it all comes down to what you value more on your trip — your money or your time — and it can be a difficult balancing act to manage the two. But mix and match to your hearts\’ content and figure out what works best for the type of trip you\’re trying to have, be it a long weekend or a gap year around the world.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="articelAuthor">
        <item>by Matthew Karsten</item>
        <item>by Natalie B. Compton</item>
        <item>by Nationwide</item>
        <item>by Carri Wilbanks</item>
        <item>by Gilad Gamliel</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>