<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Snap It</string>
    <string name="Api_key">CgB6e3x9a4NNICDnGnFCV8+aBktmeoZWbiCIcGNQgzzmkzM2oPozCF5/YlX0DsOMAdd+6rsKevlDLTYy5ROFchTz</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="ad_id_native">testu7m3hc4gvm</string>
    <string name="ad_id_native_small">testb65czjivt9</string>
    <string name="ad_id_native_video">testy63txaom86</string>
    <string name="ad_flag">Ad</string>

    <string-array name="setting_array">
        <item>Privacy Policy</item>
        <item>Logout</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="icon">
        <item>Restaurant</item>
        <item>Petrol Station</item>
        <item>Shop</item>
        <item>Museum</item>
        <item>Hotel</item>
        <item>Hospital</item>
        <item>Cinema</item>
        <item>Bank</item>
        <item>Amusement Park</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="articelTitle">
        <item>My 50 Best Travel Tips After 10 Years Traveling The World</item>
        <item>25 Things You Should Do Before Boarding a Plane, According to a Frequent Flier</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="articelContain">
        <item>
            TRAVEL TIPS GUIDE\n
            It’s now been 10 years since I sold everything and left the United States to travel the world. These are the best travel tips to help you save money and have a great trip.\n\n
            Curious about how to travel the world? I’ve been traveling around the world for many years as a digital nomad.\n\n
            <b>And I have tons of useful travel tips to share from my journey.</b>\n\n
            My traveling started when I quit my job and took a one-way flight from Miami to Guatemala, leaping nervously into the unknown and leaving much of my old life behind while embarking on an epic adventure around the world.\n\n
           <b>The experience has been a wild ride — traveling to over 50 countries, meeting countless people, and I’ve learned a ton since I first left!</b>\n\n
            Having adventures like hitchhiking across America, camping alone in Greenland, trekking through Afghanistan and much more — the world has been an amazing teacher.\n
            I eventually turned writing about my journey into a successful travel blog, and continue to travel on a regular basis as part of my dream job.\n
            But to celebrate my travelversary (travel anniversary) each year, I update this guide with a collection of my best travel tips to help you save money, stay safe, and inspire others to get out there and explore our world.\n
            And feel free to share your own favorite travel tips in the comments at the end!</item>
        <item>B</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="articelAuthor">
        <item>Matthew Karsten</item>
        <item>ERIC ROSEN</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>